landofnod.com 2017-04-21

# The Land of Nod

By sharing the Privacy Policy for Crate and Barrel, CB2 and The Land of Nod (collectively, ‘we’ or ‘us’), we hope to help you understand how information can create new opportunities for our customers, as well as to reassure you that we respect and honor customer requests to restrict and protect personal information. 

By using crateandbarrel.com, cb2.com, landofnod.com, or our mobile apps (collectively, ‘Websites’), coming to our stores, making a purchase from our catalogs, calling customer service, engaging with us on social media, interacting with us in any way, or utilizing any of our services, you consent to this Privacy Policy. 

We will comply with our Canadian Privacy Policy in our communications with all customers who are Canadian residents. 

  * Information We Collect 
  * Social Media 
  * Cookies and other Tracking Technologies 
  * How We Use Your Information 
  * Third-Party Service Providers 
  * Advertising and Online Tracking 
  * Information Sharing 
  * Your Information Sharing Choices 
  * Update Your Information 
  * Remove Your Name From Our Lists at Any Time 
  * Notice to California Residents/Your California Privacy Rights 
  * Protecting Children's Privacy 
  * Be Careful When You Share Information with Others 
  * Links to Websites and Services 
  * Compliance With Laws and Law Enforcement 
  * Information Security 
  * Your Responsibilities 
  * A Privacy Promise 
  * Processing in the United States 
  * Arbitration Agreement & Waiver of Certain Rights 
  * Privacy Policy Updates
  * Questions Anyone?

##  Information We Collect 

###  Personal Information: 

When you make a purchase in one of our stores or on our Websites or otherwise, create an account, join our Gift Registry, participate in a sweepstakes or contest or any other promotion, post a product review, engage with us on our various social media platforms, answer one of our surveys, apply for our credit card, or interact with us in any way, you may choose to give us personal information, such as: your name, email address, mailing address, ZIP code, phone number and credit card numbers. This allows us to provide you with our services, to process your transactions more efficiently and, ultimately, to give you a higher caliber of customer service. The decision to provide this information is optional. However, if you choose not to provide the requested information, you may not be able to use some or all of the features of our Websites or our services. Likewise, other companies also may forward to us additional personal information (such as, for example, names, mailing addresses and email addresses, as well as demographic and other usage information), when we have news or product offerings that may be of special interest to those individuals. We also may receive personal information through the use of social media websites and services or from other sources. 

###  Usage and Website Activity Information: 

When you visit our websites, we may collect more information: Your Internet service provider's address, the name of the Website directing you, as well as your clicks and activity on our Websites. This anonymous usage information generally is not associated with your personal information. This tracking data helps us understand how to make our Websites more available and user-friendly to our customers. 

We also gather customer information by taking note of the purchases you make. Think of it as a concierge service where customer preferences are remembered for future consideration. By looking at your purchases in context with marketing demographics or with information from companies whose products and services you may be interested in, it helps our buyers and merchandisers continue to seek out products and designs you may find relevant and unique. 

###  In-Store Information: 

We use Wi-Fi technology to track location analytics in some of our store locations. This data is used to improve the store layout and enhance the customer shopping experience in our stores. The data collected is anonymous and works by sensing the presence of smartphones. Certain device information is collected, but no personal information is collected, unless you consent to that collection. This service is provided to us by our Service Providers (defined below). To learn more about customer location and your choices from our Service Providers, visit [www.smart-places.org](https://www.smart-places.org/). We also use cameras in our stores for the same purposes and also for security and loss prevention purposes. 

Back to Top

##  Social Media 

We engage with customers on various social media platforms like Facebook, Twitter, Pinterest and Instagram. If you contact us on one of these platforms for customer service or otherwise, we may contact you via direct message. Those communications are governed by this policy as well as the policy of the relevant social media platform. 

Back to Top

##  Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies 

"Cookies" are small amounts of data that are stored on your computer. They find their way to your browser via a Web server. Cookies flag information about your activity on our Websites. This information helps us improve our Websites and make them friendlier and easier to use and allows us to market to you more effectively. We never use cookies to save passwords, credit card numbers or other highly confidential information. However, we may use them and other tracking technologies to provide enhanced online marketing based on your interests and preferences. 

To opt out of our cookies used for these personalized online ads, please click here. We will place an "opt-out cookie" on your computer should you opt out of the Service Providers who use cookies. The "opt-out cookie" is browser specific and device specific and only lasts until cookies are cleared from your browser or device. The opt-out cookie will not work for some cookies that are important to how our websites and mobile apps work ("essential cookies"). If the cookie is removed or deleted, if you upgrade your browser or if you visit us from a different computer, you will need to return to this form to re-select your preferences. If you would like to opt out of accepting cookies altogether, you can generally set your browser to not accept cookies or to notify you when you are sent a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. However, certain features of our web sites or other services may not work if you delete or disable cookies. 

Web cookies are used in some email messages and on our Websites to help us measure the effectiveness of those emails and for other analytical purposes. You can "opt out" of this email cookie at any time by deleting your name from our email mailing list(s), as detailed below. 

We also contract with a Service Provider to help us assess visitation to our Websites. To do this, we place small pixel tags and cookies on our Websites. While these do allow our Service Provider to track your visits, the data retrieved cannot be used for any reason without our authorization. Although our Service Provider logs the information about your visit, we control how that data may and may not be used. We may track this information across the different devices you use to access the Websites. You can opt out of this Website analysis tool by clicking here 

Back to Top

##  How We Use Your Information 

The personal information we collect is primarily intended to communicate with you, to offer better customer service, and to improve communications. The customer information from our brands may be combined to provide greater security and inform customers of products and services that may interest them. When a purchased item is not immediately available, many of our customers appreciate receiving an email to update the status of their order. We also may need to contact customers by phone, postal mail or email if questions arise regarding their orders. We also use personal information to send you information about products, services, and promotions that we think will be of interest to you. 

When you shop at one of our stores, order from our catalogs or visit us online, it is also an opportunity for you to provide us with information and feedback that helps us continue to bring new ideas, unique products and a creative approach to shopping for your home.

Back to Top

##  Third-Party Service Providers 

In order to serve you better, we may at times contract with other companies (“Service Providers”) to help us process information and provide other services to us. For instance, their assistance can help us fulfill customer orders, manage, store and enhance customer data, send marketing, run promotions, and provide other services. For your security, these companies are bound by our nondisclosure agreements or other contractual arrangements to provide privacy protection for your information. 

Back to Top

##  Advertising and Online Tracking 

We contract with Service Providers to place our banner advertising on other websites. These Service Providers may collect information from us about your visits to our Websites and stores, and your interaction with our products and services. They also may use this information to tailor banner advertisements for goods and services. This anonymous information is collected through the use of a pixel tag, which is technology used by major websites. Regardless of anything contrary in this Privacy Policy, personal information may be shared with our Service Provider and its service providers, including, without limitation, your name, postal address and email address, as well as a record of any transactions you conduct on our Website or offline in order to deliver banner advertisements and other advertising tailored to your interests when you visit certain websites. We may track this information across the different devices you use to access the Websites. Our trusted Service Provider will keep this data anonymous and will not share any personal information with any other third parties, except as required to provide this service. 

Our systems do not recognize browser “Do Not Track” signals, but several of our service providers who utilize these cookies and other tracking technologies on our Websites enable you to opt out of this type of advertising. To opt out of these ads, please click here . Please also visit the Network Advertising Initiative(<http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>) or the Digital Advertising Alliance (<http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>) to learn more about the use of this information by our Service Provider or to choose limited use of this information by opting out of interest-based online advertising. We also provide you with additional tools to opt out of marketing from us or certain transfers of your information. Please see the Your Information Sharing Choices section and the Remove Your Name From Our Lists at Any Time section of this Privacy Policy for more information. 

Back to Top

##  Information Sharing 

We may share your customer information with other select companies whose products and services you may find useful. These companies may contact you in order to provide you with information about these products and services. 

Information sharing also helps us to guard against potential fraud and other wrongdoing. We review transactions internally on a regular basis to identify potential concerns, and we partner with select outside companies to further enhance our ability to ensure that fraudulent orders and/or potentially damaging worms, viruses and other types of malware do not interfere with our ability to provide the best possible products, value and services to you and to our other valued customers. 

Back to Top

##  Your Information Sharing Choices 

We appreciate and respect that not all customers may wish to benefit from the opportunity to share information with other select companies. If you do not want us to share your personal information for marketing purposes, please immediately contact us and we will remove your name from lists we share with other companies. When contacting us, please clearly state your request, including your name, mailing address, email address and phone number. After we process your request, your personal information will no longer be shared for marketing purposes. 

It is important to understand that with some companies or online partners, your information must be shared in order to receive their services. 

For instance, when you order a large furniture item, we may send your name, address, email address and phone number to our shipping vendor, allowing you to access their online delivery scheduling system. Our vendor does not share your personal information with third parties; it is used strictly to coordinate and complete your shipment. 

Opting out of sharing your information for marketing purposes will not prevent your relevant information from being provided to shippers when you order products for delivery or from other sharing for non-marketing purposes. Similarly, this will not prevent us from sharing information as and to the extent it is combined or aggregated (in a non-personally identified manner) or otherwise analyzed by us or our Service Providers. 

Your information may be shared among any or all of the Crate and Barrel brands: Crate and Barrel, CB2, and The Land of Nod. 

If you have installed our mobile app, we may send push notifications to your mobile device. You can deactivate these messages at any time by changing the notification settings on your mobile device.

Back to Top

##  Update Your Information 

Updating your contact information is quick and easy. Just contact us \- include your previous and current full name, mailing address, email address and phone number or make changes directly through your account. Please understand updates may take some time to process. 

Back to Top

##  Remove Your Name From Our Lists at Any Time 

To delete your name from our email contact lists, please follow these simple email opt-out instructions. Please note that, to provide you with more control of your experience with us, opting out of one brand does not automatically opt you out of our other brands. For example, if you click through to opt out of emails from The Land of Nod, you will not be opted out of emails from Crate and Barrel or CB2; if you wish to opt out of either or both of those brands, you must visit each of their respective opt out pages and follow the opt out instructions. 

To request to have your name removed from the catalog mailing list, please complete this quick catalog opt-out form. We appreciate your patience while we process your request. When you make subsequent purchases at Crate and Barrel, CB2 or The Land of Nod, you may provide contact information for customer service only, and request that your name not be forwarded to either mailing list. If you have already opted out, you do not need to opt out again; your information will not be used for purposes other than the customer service you have requested, unless you affirmatively ask to opt in again, in which case you will be opted in and will receive emails from us until you again request to be opted out again. 

Back to Top

##  Notice to California Residents/Your California Privacy Rights 

As set forth in this Privacy Policy, we offer our customers the ability to opt out of sharing personal information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, follow  email opt-out instructions  AND / OR  catalog opt-out form , and clearly state your request, including your name, mailing address, email address and phone number. Please see the  Your Information Sharing Choices  section of this Privacy Policy for additional information. 

Back to Top

##  Protecting Children's Privacy 

We adhere to a strict privacy code regarding children and do not knowingly accept personal information from any child under the age of 13. If it is brought to our attention that we have inadvertently received personal information from a child under 13, we will immediately remove all personal and identifiable information from our records in compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998. In addition, we will not disclose this information to any other companies. California users under the age of 18 may request the removal of their content or information publically posted on the Website by e-mailing us at the appropriate brand’s customer service email address identified below. Please note that most of the user content that appears on our Website is stored and controlled by third party providers; thus, complete and comprehensive removal of the content may not be possible. 

Back to Top

##  Be Careful When You Share Information with Others 

Please be aware that whenever you share information on a publicly available area of our Websites, such as in a product review, that information may be accessed by others. In addition, please remember that when you share information in any other communications with third parties, that information may be passed along or made public by others. This means that anyone with access to such information can potentially use it for any purpose, including sending unsolicited communications. 

Back to Top

##  Links to Sites and Services 

At times, we provide links our customers may be interested in, including links to social media sites such as, for example, Facebook, Twitter or Pinterest. We are not responsible for these websites, which have their own privacy policies and privacy practices to which you may be subject. When visiting our presence on social media or other tools, you will be subject to those websites’ privacy policies. If you visit our Websites through a link from another website, you may be subject to that website’s privacy policy as well. If you choose to explore these websites and services, we suggest that you carefully review their individual privacy policies. See our Terms of Use for further information about use of social media. 

Back to Top

##  Compliance With Laws and Law Enforcement 

We cooperate with government and law-enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We may disclose personal information and any other information about you to government or law-enforcement officials or private parties if, in our discretion, we believe it is necessary or appropriate in order to respond to legal requests (including court orders and subpoenas); to protect our safety, property or rights or those of any third party; to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical or legally actionable activity; or to comply with the law. 

Back to Top

##  Information Security 

We take our customers’ personal information seriously and take steps to protect our customers' personal information against loss, misuse, alteration and unauthorized access. We use encryption technology whenever receiving and transferring your payment information on our Websites. 

### ABOUT SSL CERTIFICATES

When you make a purchase online, either a solid key or a locked padlock icon will appear in the lower right of your browser window. This icon indicates that your transaction session is secured through Secure Sockets Layer (SSL). If one of these icons does not appear, please contact us at (800) 967-6696 to complete your purchase. 

Back to Top

##  Your Responsibilities 

You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account and password and for restricting access to your computer. You are responsible for all activities that occur under your account or password. As a result, it is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a computer that others may have access to. 

Back to Top

##  A Privacy Promise 

We support and adhere to the guidelines and practices adopted by the Direct Marketing Association's Privacy Promise and the Digital Advertising Alliance Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising. In doing so, we agree to comply with a customer's requests to not share their information with other companies or to contact them for marketing purposes by postal mail, telephone, email or through online behavioral advertising. 

If at any time, as a customer, you believe we are not committed to its Privacy Policy, please contact us. You also may contact the DMA’s Committee on Ethical Business Practices at [mgoldberger@the-dma.org](mailto:mgoldberger@the-dma.org). 

Back to Top

##  Processing in the United States 

Please be aware that your personal information and communications may be transferred to and maintained on servers or databases located outside your state, province or country. If you are located outside the United States, please be advised that we process and store all information in the United States. The laws in the United States may not be as protective of your privacy as those in your location. By using our Websites or our services, you agree that the collection, use, transfer and disclosure of your personal information and communications will be governed by the applicable laws in the United States. 

Back to Top

##  Arbitration Agreement & Waiver of Certain Rights 

You and we agree that we will resolve any disputes between us through binding and final arbitration instead of through court proceedings. You and we hereby waive any right to a jury trial of any Claim. All controversies, claims, counterclaims, or other disputes arising between you and us relating to this Privacy Policy or the Websites (each a "Claim") shall be submitted for binding arbitration in accordance with the Rules of the American Arbitration Association ("AAA Rules"). The arbitration will be heard and determined by a single arbitrator. The arbitrator's decision in any such arbitration will be final and binding upon the parties and may be enforced in any court of competent jurisdiction. The parties agree that the arbitration will be kept confidential and that the existence of the proceeding and any element of it (including, without limitation, any pleadings, briefs or other documents submitted or exchanged and any testimony or other oral submissions and awards) will not be disclosed beyond the arbitration proceedings, except as may lawfully be required in judicial proceedings relating to the arbitration or by applicable disclosure rules and regulations of securities regulatory authorities or other governmental agencies. 

If you demonstrate that the costs of arbitration will be prohibitive as compared to the costs of litigation, we will pay as much of the administrative costs and arbitrator's fees required for the arbitration as the arbitrator deems necessary to prevent the cost of the arbitration from being prohibitive. In the final award, the arbitrator may apportion the costs of arbitration and the compensation of the arbitrator among the parties in such amounts as the arbitrator deems appropriate. 

This arbitration agreement does not preclude you or us from seeking action by federal, state, or local government agencies. You and we also have the right to bring qualifying claims in small claims court. In addition, you and we retain the right to apply to any court of competent jurisdiction for provisional relief, including pre-arbitral attachments or preliminary injunctions, and any such request shall not be deemed incompatible with this Privacy Policy, nor a waiver of the right to have disputes submitted to arbitration as provided in this Privacy Policy. 

Neither you nor we may act as a class representative or private attorney general, nor participate as a member of a class of claimants, with respect to any Claim. Claims may not be arbitrated on a class or representative basis. The arbitrator can decide only your and/or our individual Claims. The arbitrator may not consolidate or join the claims of other persons or parties who may be similarly situated. 

If any provision of this Section is found to be invalid or unenforceable, then that specific provision shall be of no force and effect and shall be severed, but the remainder of this Section shall continue in full force and effect. No waiver of any provision of this Section of the Privacy Policy will be effective or enforceable unless recorded in a writing signed by the party waiving such a right or requirement. Such a waiver shall not waive or affect any other portion of this Privacy Policy. This Section of the Privacy Policy will survive the termination of your relationship with us. 

THIS SECTION LIMITS CERTAIN RIGHTS, INCLUDING THE RIGHT TO MAINTAIN A COURT ACTION, THE RIGHT TO A JURY TRIAL, THE RIGHT TO PARTICIPATE IN ANY FORM OF CLASS OR REPRESENTATIVE CLAIM, THE RIGHT TO ENGAGE IN DISCOVERY EXCEPT AS PROVIDED IN AAA RULES, AND THE RIGHT TO CERTAIN REMEDIES AND FORMS OF RELIEF. OTHER RIGHTS THAT YOU OR WE WOULD HAVE IN COURT ALSO MAY NOT BE AVAILABLE IN ARBITRATION. 

Back to Top

##  Privacy Policy Updates 

Efforts to bring new services, ideas and partners to benefit our customers may make it necessary to amend our Privacy Policy. If this occurs, we will post the new policy on our Websites and in our stores. Once posted, the new policy will go into effect immediately, replacing any previously stated policy. Your continued use of our Websites or services constitutes your consent to the revised Privacy Policy. 

Back to Top

##  Questions Anyone? 

If you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy, we will do our best to answer them. Here's how to contact us : 

**Phone:**  
Customer Service Department  
Monday - Sunday, 7 days a week

**Email:**  

**Address:**  
The Land of Nod  
Customer Service Department  
8135 River Drive  
Morton Grove, IL 60053 

Back to Top

_Last Updated, February 8, 2017_
